你在越南害怕过吗？
were you scared in Vietnam?
是的
Yes.
我…
Well, I...
我不知道
I don't know.
当雨停的时候
Sometimes it would stop raining
有时能看到星星…
long enough for the stars to come out...
那感觉很好
and then it was nice.
就像太阳下山前
It was like just before the sun goes to bed
在拉巴特湾
down on the bayou.
海面的闪闪鳞光…
there was always a million sparkles on the water...
就像山间的湖水
like that mountain lake.
那样的清澈 珍妮
It was so clear, Jenny,
就像另一片天空
it looked like there were two skies
两重天空
one on top of the other.
还有在沙漠里 当太阳升起…
And then in the desert, when the sun comes up...
我分不清
I couldn't tell
哪儿是天 哪儿是地
where heaven stopped and the earth began.
真是美丽
It's so beautiful.
我但愿那时和你在一起
I wish I could've been there with you.